Welcome to the course.
Deployment of machine learning mothers.
My name is Soledad legally and I am an experienced data scientist.
I have pit mothers to assess credit risk and to prevent fraud and also to handle multiple aspects of
insurance claims.
I like sharing machine learning knowledge through talks blogs and articles and I'm also an instructor
in you that me and I'm Chris Samuels.
I'm an experienced machine learning software engineer and I've built code to deploy multiple machine
learning models to serve hundreds of thousands of customers.
Chris and I have worked together on multiple occasions to build and deploy models for credit risk and
fraud prevention.
And now we have teamed up to bring you a course that will allow you to deploy your own machine learning
models in this course you will learn how to take your machine learning models from the research stage
to a fully integrated API that can be caught live and utilized on life data to make predictions.
No machine learning model brings true value until it is fully integrated and can be used to score real
data.
So model deployment is the most important and yet most difficult part of any typical machine learning
pipeline.
By the end of this course you will know all the necessary steps and things you need to consider to deploy
a machine learning model.
What is more the deployment model deployment is the process of integrating a machine learning model
into an existing production environment so that we can use it to make business decisions based alive
or future data.
It is one of the latest stages in the machine learning pipeline and potentially the most challenging.
Why is more than deployment so important.
For a business to be able to leverage the power of a machine learning model the model needs to be fully
deployed into production.
If we cannot get practical insight from the model that is if we cannot score like data or real data
with it then the impact of the model is severely limited.
Model deployment is one of the most difficult processes in the machine learning pipeline and also the
one that will allow us to extract real value from our mother mother deployment requires coordination
between data scientists I.T. teams and their ops software developers and business professionals to make
sure the model works reliably in their organization's production environment this represents a major
challenge because there is often a discrepancy between the programming language in which the machine
learning model is written and the languages your production system can understand and record in the
model can extend the project timeline by weeks or months in order to get the most value out of the machine
learning mothers.
It is important to deploy them into production as seamlessly as possible so the business can start using
them to make practical decisions.
So why should you take this course in this course.
We are going to take you through the entire machine learning lifecycle.
We will start with building a machine learning model utilizing Jupiter and notebooks which is what most
data scientists are used to.
Then you will learn how to transform that code into code that can be used in production.
So first we will show you the best practices around writing production code and then you will learn
how to create an API and make calls to the API.
Then we'll introduce you to testing to corroborate that research and production models produced the
same outcome given the same data you learn about continuous integration.
And finally we will cover various deployment solutions available to you such as platform as a service
or infrastructure as a service.
You will also learn about how to use Docker to ensure model reproducibility and robustness.
Who is this course for deployment of machine learning mothers requires a concerted effort among data
scientists software developers data engineers and business domain experts.
This course offers something new and useful for all of these professionals the cause is ideally suited
for intermediate and advanced data scientists.
If you have already built a few Machine Learning mothers and are familiar with the different steps required
to read the modern like feature engineering feature selection and would like guidance deploying mothers
to production then this is the course for you.
The course is also suitable for data engineers wanting to integrate mother production and AP ice into
their existing data pipelines this course is also suitable for software developers that want to expand
their skills to step into a development and finally as we use mostly open source tools.
This course is also suitable for open source lovers.
So what will you take home from this course.
In this course you will get more than eight hours of video content and lifetime access to the lectures
you will take.
Ready to use code and deploy your machine learning models using this code the code will be suitable
to create and expand your models in production with tests and error handling.
Also you'll be provided with code to build the API eyes and make calls to them with life data.
You will learn how to containerized your applications using Docker and we will guide you through deploying
your machine learning systems onto both platform as a service and infrastructure as a service.
Cloud computing solutions.
Finally we also include links and references to what other companies are doing worldwide to smooth and
streamline their machine learning pipelines.
So would you like to know more about the course check the next video for the complete course curriculum
and in the unlikely event that you don't find the course useful.
There is a 30 day money back guarantee.
So what are you waiting for.
And well today learn how to put your machine learning models live and start getting true value from
your machine learning models.