Welcome to the lecture on knowledge requirements.
In this video you can learn the knowledge you should have to make the most out of this course the courses
tailored to students with some knowledge of data science.
You should be familiar with the meaning of feature engineering and feature selection and why it is important
and you should also know at least the most commonly used machine learning algorithms like linear and
logistic regression and Random Forests.
You should also know how to evaluate the performance of a machine learning algorithm in the course we
will deploy a linear regression model and in the last section we will deploy a convolution of neural
network.
It will be helpful for you to understand what a linear regression is although you don't necessarily
need to be familiar with deep learning to follow on with Section 13 in Section 2.
We give you a quite extensive overview on the different steps of the machine learning pipeline including
what feature engineering is and what feature selection is and why they are important.
However it is not within the scope of the course to teach you the different ways in which you can engineer
and select your features.
It is also not within the scope of the course to teach what the different algorithms are and what deep
learning is.
So here we will focus mostly on the deployment aspect of things only covering things about machine learning
when they are important for more deployment.
If you feel you need to learn more about any of the things in this slide we have included plenty of
additional resources that you can use to level up your skills.
And of course you can always ask questions in the forums.
You should also have a good Python programming skills in particularly around libraries for numerical
computing and machine learning.
We will capitalize on the use of the could learn pipeline so the more familiar you are with site could
learn the most you will get out of the course if you're not extremely familiar though.
Don't worry we have included plenty of resources to brush up your skills.
This might mean that you will need extra time to fully understand the code we present in this course.
But by no means it means that you won't be able to get to the result desired which is deploying your
mothers in this course.
We're going to use a python three point six installation if you don't have one.
You can get it following the link in this slide.
Any other Python three point six installation will also do the trick and we're going to tell more about
packaged versions and environments in dedicated lectures throughout the course.
We will be using datasets publicly available in Kaggle so you will need to set up a Kaggle account which
is totally free and will allow you to access to all the data sets and competitions available in Kaggle
to try your newly acquired skills.
Finally it is important for water deployment to work in dedicated environments and use it to track code
version.
Therefore knowledge of these skills will be highly beneficial for you.
We do however include a section to refresh on the use of environments and the use of it which can help
you get started and follow through the course.
In that section we will also include plenty of resources where you can learn more about environments
and the use of IT in general.
So let's go ahead and get started.